Guide to the Joel T. Broyhill papers, 1952-1974
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Joel T. Broyhill papers
1952-1974
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Broyhill, Joel T. (Joel Thomas), 1919-2006.
C0088
34.25 linear feet (66 boxes)
This collection contains documents pertaining to Joel Broyhill's career as a U.S. Congressman representing Virginia's 10th district. Materials in the collection deriving from his career as a legislator include bills, House resolutions, official records, press releases, Congressional (83rd-93rd) newsletters, papers, personal correspondence, newspaper clippings, schedules, and budgets.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Joel T. Broyhill and Virginia Lampe in 1985-1988.
Biographical Information
Joel Thomas Broyhill was born in Hopewell, Virginia, in 1919. After graduating from George Washington University in 1941, Broyhill served as a captain and rifle company commander for the U.S. Army during World War II. His service in Germany, which included capture during the Battle of the Bulge and escape from a prisoner-of-war camp, earned him a bronze star. After the war, Broyhill returned to Arlington, Virginia, to work as a partner and general manager of his father's real-estate business, M.T. Broyhill and Sons, which flourished during the post-War suburban economic boom.
Broyhill won his seat in Congress in 1952, the year of Dwight D. Eisenhower's presidential landslide. During his career as state representative, Broyhill became an influential member of the House District Committee and a master of legislative strategy. Best known for local matters, Broyhill sponsored legislation that led to the construction of the Roosevelt and Woodrow Wilson bridges across the Potomac River and the second span of the 14th Street Bridge, as well as a measure that led to the widening of Shirley Highway. He fought for better pay and working conditions for federal employees, federal aid to local school systems and financial support for Metro. Broyhill was also an unrelenting and outspoken opponent of "home rule" for the District of Columbia, arguing that the U.S. Constitution placed ultimate responsibility for the nation's capital with Congress, and he battled for years against measures to increase the authority of city residents to manage D.C. affairs. In 1974, in the wake of the Watergate scandal and the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon, Broyhill lost his seat to Democrat Joseph L. Fisher.
After losing his seat in Congress, Broyhill served as campaign manager for John W. Warner's successful first campaign for the Senate and returned to work for his family's real-estate development and investment company. On September 24, 2006, Broyhill died of congestive heart failure and pneumonia at his home in Arlington.
Scope and Content
This collection contains documents pertaining to Joel Broyhill's career as a U.S. Congressman representing Virginia's 10th district. The campaign publications included therein offer a detailed look at the election campaigns of Congressman Broyhill in the 1960s and early 1970s. Materials in the collection deriving from his career as a legislator include bills, House resolutions, official records, press releases, Congressional (83rd-93rd) newsletters, papers, personal correspondence, newspaper clippings, schedules, and budgets.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically and by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collection and Archives also holds many other collections on Northern Virginia politics and government including the.
Index Terms
Persons:
Broyhill, Joel T. (Joel Thomas), 1919-2006.
Corporate Names:
United States. Congress. House.
Geographical Names:
Virginia--Politics and government.
Subjects:
Political campaigns--Virginia.
Contents List
  - BZA - #9452 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - BZA - #10110 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Housing Development Corporation (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Housing Development Corp papers (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Housing Development Corporation (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Housing Development Corp-Newspaper Clippings (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clifton Terrace Scandal-Newspaper Clipping, Booklet (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Release of Studies on Household Patterns and Governmental policies (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Energy research and development, July '73 (booklet). Technology review, June '73 (magazine), June - July, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letters opposing Tax Reform Act of 1974 (taxing disabled veterans benefits) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letters opposing Tax Reform Act of 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters opposing Tax Reform Act of 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Letters supporting 3-Point program for Housing construction (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Letters supporting 3-Point program for Housing construction (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Welfare (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Abortions (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Airports (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Army [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Army [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Picture of Bridge (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - JTB (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Civil Service (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Incinerator / power and steam take off (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Drugs (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - FDA (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gun Control (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Health (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Health Ins. Proposal 92nd Congress (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Jobs (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Labor Certification (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Medicare (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Monday Holiday Law (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pollution in Virginia (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Post office (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Potomac river (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Revenue sharing (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Selective Service (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - S.B.A. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Schools (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Social Security (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - State Income taxes of Virginia (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Student unrest in US (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Student aid and medical school (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Summer Employment (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Transportation (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Treasury (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Veterans education (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Wage and price freeze (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - News Letters, September 1969, June 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Environment, March 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Subway, May 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commuter Tax, August 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Drugs and China, September 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, UN, November 1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaire, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter-Revenue Sharing and Route 66, April 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Tax Reform, June 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Metro, August 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, February and April 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter-Federal Spending, Aid, Vietnam, March 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter, April 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter, May 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter, June 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter, September 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Newsletter, October 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter, January 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Newsletter, May 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, June 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter, August 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Newsletter, September 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 83rd Congress-Bills Public and Private (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 84th Congress, 2nd Session - Bills Public and Private (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 84th Congress, 1st Session - Public Bills (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 85th Congress, All Bills (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 84th Congress, All Bills (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 86th Congress, All Bills (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 86th Congress (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 87th Congress - Private Bills and Resolutions (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 87th Congress Private Bills (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 88th Congress Public (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 88th Congress Private (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 89th Congress Public (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 89th Congress Public (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 89th Congress PVT and RES (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 90th Congress Public Bills (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Public Bills (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Public Bills (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 91st Congress 2nd Session Public Bills (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 91st Congress 2nd Session Public Bills (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 91st Congress PVT and RES (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 90th Congress Public (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 90th Congress Public Bills (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 90th Congress PVT and RES (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 90th Congress PVT and RES (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Private Bills and Resolutions (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Private Bills and Resolutions (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Public Bills (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Public Bills (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 92nd Congress 1st Session Public Bills (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - HR 10873 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - HR 10922 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - HR 10937 [1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - HR 10937 [2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - HR 11120 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - HR 11193 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - HR 11215 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - HR 11311 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - HR 11312 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - HR 11313 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - HR 11403 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - HR 11517 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - HR 11802 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - HR 12311 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - HR 12348 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - HR 12599 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - HR 12600 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - HR 12854 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - HR 12855 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - HR 12856 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - HR 12891 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - HR 13113 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - HR 13240 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - HR 13270 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - HR 13420 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - HR 13837 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - HR 13562 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - HR 13982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - HR 14173 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - HR 14189 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - HR 14307 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - HR 14493 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - HR 14715 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - HR 14784 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - HR 14875 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - HR 14877 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - HR 14939 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - HR 14982 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - HR 14998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - HR 15033 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - HR 15151 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - HR 15179 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - HR 15370 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - HR 15555 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - HR 15587 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - HR 15622 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - HR 15690 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - HR 15902 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - HR 15936 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - HR 15972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - HR 15980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - HR (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - HR 16238 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - HR 16239 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - HR 16240 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - HR 16241 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - HR 16242 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - HR 16243 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - HR 16319 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - HR 16741 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - HR 16988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - HR 16237 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - HR 17096 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - HR 17138 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - HR 17197 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - HR 17349 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - HR 17408 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - HR 17601 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - HR 17694 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - HR 17710 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - HR 17754 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - HR 18007 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - HR 1844 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - HR 18485 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - HR 18562 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - HR 18563 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - HR 18567 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - HR 18568 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - HR 18602 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - HR 18663 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - HR 18752 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - HR 18782 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - HR 18783 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - HR 18801 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - HR 18878 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - HR 18915 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - HR 19454 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - HR 19561 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - HR 19842 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - HR 19939 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - HJ Res 26 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - HJ Res 293 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - H Con Res 332 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - H Con Res 340 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - H Con Res 358 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - H Con Res 360 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - HJ Res 388 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - H Con Res 560 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - H Res 678 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - H Res 731 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - H res 779 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - HJ Res 895 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - H Res 913 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - HJ Res 947 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - HJ Res 1121 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - HJ Res 1166 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - HJ Res 1231 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - H Res 1279 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - H Res 1282 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - H res 1326 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 2835 HR (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 2834 HR (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - HR (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - HR (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 3722 HR (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 3723 HR (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 3724 HR (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - 4665 HR (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - 4666 HR (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - 4667 HR (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - 4980 HR (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 4981 HR (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - 4982 HR (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 11628 HR (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - 4983 HR (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - 4984 HR (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - 4985 HR (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - 4985 HR (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - 4987 HR (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - 4988 HR (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - 4989 HR (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - 6113 HR (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 6114 HR (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 6115 HR (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 6116 HR (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 6117 HR (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 6574 HR (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 6575 HR (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 7232 HR (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 7809 HR (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 8230 HR (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 8231 HR (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 8468 HR (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - 8558 HR (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 9588 HR (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 9813 HR (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 10357 HR (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 11301 HR (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 12620 HR (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - 12621 HR (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 12622 HR (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 12716 HR (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 13917 HR (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 17865 HR (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 18001 HR (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 18887 HR (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 18888 HR (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 19105 HR (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 19148 HR (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 19219 HR (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 19441 HR (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 19875 HR (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - 19940 HR (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - 11657 HR (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - 11890 HR (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - 11935 HR (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - 12115 HR (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - 11841 HR (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - 11877 HR (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - 12162 HR (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - 12182 HR (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - 12183 HR (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - 12263 HR (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - 12297 HR (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - 12543 HR (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - 12544 HR (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - 12562 HR (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - 12625 HR (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - 12703 HR (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Leftover From GCM-AMA Proceedings House of Delegates Re: Bill to Amend Social Security Act (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - PIPO, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Personnel File (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - National Land Use Policy, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Republican Congressional Newsletter, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Republican Policy Statements (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Veteran Administration Cemetery Information (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - White House Release, September 10, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - L B (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - NASA (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - National Capitol Transportation Authority (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - OEO (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - P.O. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - R R B (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - State Income taxes of Virginia (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Transportation (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Treasury (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Virginia (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Pollution, Environment, Ecology (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rapid Transit for Washington, D.C. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hr 18970 91st Congress 2nd Session (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - HR 4664 91st Congress 1st Session (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rapid Rail Notes (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - HR 15099 92nd Congress 2nd Session (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 93rd Congress 2nd Session Public Bills (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Yearbook (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Interior Pollution (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - A of A (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Commerce (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Army (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Commerce - Population (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Civil Service Commission (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - D.C. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Defense (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - F.A.A. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - F.C.C. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - F.T.C. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - HEW - Social Security (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Interior (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Interior Pollution (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Judiciary (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Justice (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - HEW (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - HUD (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - JTB Inquiry (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Labor (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bill Folder, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - A, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - B, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - C, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - D, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - E, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - F, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - G, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - H, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - J, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - K, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - L, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - M, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - N, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - O, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - P, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - R, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - S, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - T, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - U, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - V, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - W, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Y, 1973 - 1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - HR 1824 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - HR 1825 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - HR 1826 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - HR 1827 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - HR 1828 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - HR 2391 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - HR 2392 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - HR 2393 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - HR 2695 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - HR 3392 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - HR 3732 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - HR 5141 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - HR 5301 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - HR 5669 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - HR 6204 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - HR 7156 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - HR 7157 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - HR 7307 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - HR 8019 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - HR 8219 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - HR 9390 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - HR 9472 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - HR 9515 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - HR 9516 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - HR 10924 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - HR 11388 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - HR 11463 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - HR 11679 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - HR 13491 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - HR 14571 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - HR 14875 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - HR 15723 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - HR 15518 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - HR 16207 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - HR 16208 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - HR 16785 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - HR 18494 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - HJ Res 4 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - HJ Res 18 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - HJ Res 26 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - HJ res 107 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - H Con Res 154 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - HJ Res 197 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - H Res 328 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - H Con Res 360 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - H res 375 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - H Res 401 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - H Con Res 467 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - H Res 500 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - HJ Res 503 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - H Res 596 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - H Res 613 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - HJ Res 123 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - HJ Res 123 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - HJ Res 651 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - HJ Res 700 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - HJ Res 733 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - HJ Res 912 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - HJ Res 931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - HJ Res 982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - HJ Res 993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - HJ Res 1232 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - HR 109 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - HR 110 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - HR 112 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - HR 113 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - HR 139 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - HR 615 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - HR 2293 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - HR 3489 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - HR 3543 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - HR 4216 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - HR 4264 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - HR 4922 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - HR 4960 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - HR 4961 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - HR 4962 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - HR 4963 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - HR 5252 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - HR 5254 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - HR 5593 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - HR 5628 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - HR 5635 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - HR 5810 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - HR 5993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - HR 5960 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - HR 5964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - HR 5968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - HR 5972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - HR 6119 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - HR 6328 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - HR 6917 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - HR 6952 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - HR 6954 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - HR 7092 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - HR 7177 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - HR 7267 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - HR 7332 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - HR 7611 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - HR 7804 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - HR 7806 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - HR 7807 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - HR 7931 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - HR 7939 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - HR 7958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - HR 7964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - HR 8038 [1 of 2] (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - HR 8038 [2 of 2] (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - HR 8375 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - HR 8376 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - HR 8377 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - HR 8407 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - HR 8408 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - HR 8409 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - HR 8410 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - HR 8411 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - HR 8589 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - HR 8684 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - HR 8794 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - HR 8890 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - HR 8891 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - HR 8892 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - HR 8975 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - HR 9039 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - HR 9082 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - HR 9176 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - HR 9216 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - HR 9395 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - HR 9427 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - HR 9529 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - HR 9555 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - HR 9580 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - HR 9604 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - HR 9605 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - HR 9863 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - HR 10019 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - HR 10065 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - HR 10185 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - HR 10211 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - HR 10264 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - HR 10383 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - HR 10573 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - HR 10574 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - HR 10595 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - HR 10661 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - HR 10738 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - HR 10774 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - HR 10775 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - HR 10784 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - HR 10809 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - HR 10810 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - HR 10841 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - HR 10881 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - HR 11032 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - HR 11126 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - HR 11131 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - HR 11268 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - HR 11313 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - HR 11348 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - HR 11349 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - HR 11369 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - HR 11444 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - HR 11492 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - HR 11612 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - HR 12710 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - HR 12771 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - HR 12772 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - HR 13019 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - HR 13318 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - HR 13366 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - HR 13411 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - HR 13413 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - HR 13713 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - HR 14308 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - HR 14419 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - HR 14507 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - HR 14508 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - HR 14509 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - HR 14718 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - HR 14845 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - HR 14869 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - HR 15061 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - HR 15157 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - HR 15194 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - HR 15281 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - HR 15442 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - HR 15507 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - HR 15550 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - HR 15598 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - HR 15612 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - HR 15622 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - HR 15664 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - HR 15711 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - HR 15761 (Box 37, Folder 8)